His fast-acting mind is one reason.
Wake up!
If you start napping now, it's gonna
be hard to get to sleep tonight.
There's three days of winter break left
and your homework won't finish itself.
Sinon finished hers before
heading back home to visit.
Just saying I'm so sleepy poor thing it's
probably because the room's too warm.
You want me to turn down the heat?
It's not the heat it's the masters
of the sleep skill over there huh?
Oh well that figures.
He's been working hard on his project
ever since he got back from GGO.
You mean that gizmo for Yui he
demoed the other day at Egil's?
Oh, the mechaphonics?
No, it's called mechatronics.
Uh, yeah, that.
Anyway, he's napping
like there's no tomorrow.
Look at him.
He's making me feel sleepy.
Hmm.
I don't know what the name is.
It's a picture of the sky.
I call it the voice.
It's from the
beginning of this story.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
You've been looking at the future.
I'll give it for my way.
Here you go.
Yo, guys, seriously.
Y 'all don't have to come here
every time you're on a date.
There's classier places
in town you could go to.
What are you talking about?
This place is plenty classy.
Compared to your shop in Allgate, anyway.
Oh, don't listen to him. I liked it.
That place was a rip-off.
Half that junk was papier-mâché.
How can you say that?
He was letting you stay there for free.
That's got nothing to do with it.
Oh, whatever.
Okay, Spill It, what's so funny?
Nothing.
Just, seeing you like this,
y 'all don't look anything like
the Assault Team's top players.
Right back at you, buddy.
Well, on that note, I bet you've
played MMORPGs for a long time, huh?
True that.
I played so much, I met the Mrs.
in-game.
She used to live in the U .S.,
and we fell for each other hard.
A year later, she was here,
running the place with me.
Y 'all never know what life's
got planned for you. Aww.
If Klein heard that story,
he'd pop a blood vessel.
Anyway, we got married.
Next big step was getting
ourselves a pair of NerveGear rigs.
But when the time came, we
could only pre-order one.
I remember we played some game
to see who'd get to try it first.
I'm glad it was me who cracked
the seal on it, not her.
Still feel that way.
The assault team was the only ticket out.
That's why I joined up with them.
All I wanted was to get back
to this place and to my lady.
I know what you mean.
I wanted to get back to my family, too.
It's what kept me alive in there.
You and the assault team, brother.
Hell, man.
I bet every player in Ironcrat felt
the same way about going home again.
Right, Asuna?
Ain't that what motivated you?
No, not really.
I mean, it's complicated
between me and my family.
I guess that's why there
were a couple times in
there I almost forgot
what I was fighting for.
Sometimes I felt like I
didn't belong anywhere.
Real and virtual were both dead ends.
But then, I met Kirito.
He gave me something I could come home to.
A place that felt more like a home.
Than anything I ever
had in the real world.
I was happy.
Even though I knew once SAO was cleared.
Our cabin would be gone.
But I knew deep down
that one day, somehow.
I'd have a home again with Kirito and Yui.
That's what finally gave
me the strength to fight.
And keep fighting.
It gave me hope?
Speaking of Ironcrad kiddies, the mod's
just posted some info on the next update.
It's mostly typical stuff.
They're going to be adding
new weapons and sword skills,
but they're also going to be unlocking
floors 21 to 30 in new Ironcrad. Boom.
Wait, do you know what that means?
If we beat the boss on Floor 21, we have
a chance to buy that log cabin again.
Yeah, yeah, but there's been a ton of
little changes to New Aincrad lately.
It sucked to get our hopes up just
to find our cabin's not there.
Yeah, it would, but I know it's there.
It'll be waiting for us,
just like how we left it.
Well, y 'all better get a move on then.
Update goes live Christmas Eve.
Seiya, Sha, Lindo, Ashina,
Bart, Amy, or Sparrow!
Ah!
Ah! Ha! Ha! Ha!
I'm going in!
Asuna, keep going!
I've got your back!
Asuna, you and me!
Watch out, Daddy!
It's about to punch!
Watch out!
I beat ya!
Whoa!
All right!
We made it to floor 22!
Hey, Asuna.
If you're hanging around because
of the teleport gate, don't bother.
We can activate it.
Thanks a lot, you guys!
Are you seeing this?
Here we go. Are you ready?
I don't know.
I'm home.
Oh, my God, seriously?
Hey, Asuna, wake up!
That goes for you, too!
God, would you look at that?
It's like he's daring us to stay awake.
I'll make some more tea,
and it'll wake us right up.
Hey, look!
I guess it stopped snowing
while we were sleeping.
Yeah, it really came down.
Oh, have you heard the news? What?
You know, about Second.
Don't tell me you haven't heard.
Second?
Is that some kind of
rare item or something?
Er, wrong.
It's the name of a player.
Actually, it's not their handle,
it's more like a nickname.
Anyway, this player's so bad-ass,
someone called him Zekken.
The name caught on and there you go.
It means absolute sword.
Ultimate sword's better, though.
Either way, this player's tough.
Really?
So, uh, when did you first
hear about this second person?
I don't know.
I guess maybe the first time was
around New Year's or something.
Maybe a week or so ago? Oh, duh.
That explains why you're so
out of the loop about it.
You've been at your family's
compound in Kyoto this whole time.
Mama.
I was having a good time,
but you had to bring that up.
Listen to the rich girl
rebelling against her cushy life.
Sounds like a drag.
A drag is exactly what it was.
I had to sit on my knees in a
kimono all day greeting people.
I brought my Amusphere along,
thinking I could dive at night
while everyone was asleep.
But you know what?
The guesthouse I was in
didn't have Wi-Fi. Fun, right?
It wasn't.
Asuna?
You even listening? Hello?
Huh? S-sorry.
I just remembered something lame.
I wonder what that could be.
Were your folks trying to
hook you up with someone?
No, not at all.
Forget I said anything.
Okay, okay, just kidding.
So, anyway, is this
tough new player a PKer?
something? Mama.
Just a duelist, that's all.
Were they in any tournaments? Nope.
As far as I know,
those players are total noob.
I have a feeling they might have
converted over from another game,
though.
You should see their skill stats.
They're through the roof.
You know how on floor 24 there's that tiny
little island just north of the main town?
The one with the huge tree.
Well, every day at three o 'clock,
you-know-who shows up under that tree,
waiting to take on any challenger one-on-one.
Zeken started by posting
this opponent's wanted
notice on the MMO Tomorrow bulletin board.
Folks wanted to teach this cocky ALL
noobah lesson, so on the first day,
about 30 players showed up.
It didn't go so well for him, though.
What? They lost? All of them.
One after the other.
And get this.
None of them managed to chip off
more than 30 % of Zeken's HP.
That's a badass.
I can't believe how good Zekken is.
Who thought a newbie to the
game could fly as good as that?
It took me at least six months to learn
how to fly and fight at the same time.
And I'm still learning stuff.
I did it!
Did you fight Zekken too? Not even.
I'm no dummy.
I watched one duel and I
knew I didn't stand a chance.
If you want to know what it was like,
why don't you ask Liz and Leafa?
They took Zekken on yesterday.
They fought and lost
like a couple of champs.
Please don't remind me.
Good learning experience, though.
It's snowing.
Yeah, pretty, isn't it?
So anyway, back to Zekken.
If this player is as strong as you say,
it's only a matter of time before
there are no more challengers to face.
I don't know about that.
There's a pretty cool prize
on the line, don't you know?
Really?
What is it?
Some kind of rare item or something?
Nope, it's nothing like that.
Whoever beats second will
get an original sword skill.
It's a special move that's
supposed to be super strong.
An original sword skill?
What type?
How many hits?
Well, it's a general skill
for a one-handed sword.
Oh, but here's the thing.
It's an Head combo.
No way, 11?
The strongest original sword skill being
used right now, how many hits does it have?
That'd be the one General Eugene
developed, the Volcanic Blazer.
It's supposed to be an eight-hit combo.
He hasn't passed it on to anyone
else yet, and I doubt he ever will.
I guess that explains why so many players
keep lining up to challenge Second.
Have any of you seen this
sword skill in action?
Mama.
I heard Second demoed it on the
first day of the duels, though.
Apparently it blew mines left and right.
But since then, it hasn't been
used in any of the fights.
Maybe the reason for
that's because there hasn't
been anyone tough enough
to get Zekken to use it.
Whoever does has my respect.
Leafa, what happened
when you fought Zekken?
Besides losing?
It was going good till
our HPs dropped below 60%.
But...
In the end, Zekken beat me,
using nothing but default skills.
Really?
Oh, I can't believe I
almost forgot to ask.
What's Zekin's race and
weapon of choice? An imp.
The main weapon's a one-handed sword.
It's about as skinny as your
rapier, Asuna, but only just.
And Zekin's super fast, too.
I couldn't even see the
attacks coming at me.
That's never happened to me before.
I'm still kind of shocked.
A speed type, huh?
If you had a hard time tracking
second, I doubt I'd be able to either.
I know someone who might, though.
Mr.
Sleepyhead's the fastest player I've seen.
What do you guys think?
Would Kirito go for
that kind of challenge?
What?
What'd I say?
Nothing, it's just
Kazuto already tried it.
And boy, did he lose spectacularly.
I don't believe it.
Was he holding back?
Hmm.
Kind of hard for me to say.
From where I was standing,
it looked like it.
Yeah,
but then I don't think I'm really the best
person to judge whether he was or wasn't.
He didn't use that dual-wielding
trick, that's for sure.
So I guess in a way, he
wasn't going all out.
But you know what?
That kind of makes sense.
I mean, it's a duel in a normal game.
There's no reason for Kitty to do a fight
like his life depended on it anymore.
The only time he'll take a fight seriously
now is if the game stops being a game.
When the virtual world
becomes the real world.
In a way, I hope he never goes
full tilt in a battle ever again.
He's kind of had enough of that.
I mean, heck, he gets into enough
trouble on his own as it is.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Well, from where I was standing,
I got a different impression.
I think Kazuto was
definitely giving it his all.
He seemed serious and
focused and determined.
He put up a good fight.
At one point, though,
something weird happened.
Right before the duel was
over, they were locking swords.
And then, they both just stopped.
It looked like Kazuto was
saying something to Zekken.
I couldn't hear what
because of all the cheering.
And then, all of a sudden, they
backed off from each other.
Zekken charged him, but Kazuto couldn't
dodge it, and that's how the duel ended.
Really?
What were they talking about?
I wish I knew.
I asked him, but Kazuto wouldn't tell me.
Whatever it was, it must be pretty
important to keep to himself.
Interesting.
All right then,
I guess the only way to find out
what he said is to ask Zekken myself.
Huh.
You think you're up to the challenge?
I'm not doing it because
I think I can win.
Something about this second
person intrigues me is all.
I don't know why,
but I think this second person's
here for reasons other than dueling.
Yep, that's what I think too.
But if you want to find
out what it is, get ready,
because you're going to have to put
up as good a fight as your boy Kirito,
and then some.
Yeah, I know.
Will you guys come cheer me on?
You know we will. It'll be awesome.
We wouldn't miss it for anything.
Which character are
you going to duel with?
You still have that
Sylph account, don't you?
Hmm.
I guess I'll use this one.
If Zekin's a speed type,
it'll probably come down to who can
hold out the longest rather than DPS.
And that's that.
So, 3 o 'clock on the island
on Floor 24, right? Mm-hmm.
Then if we meet here tomorrow
at 2.30, we can... Oh, no!
It's already 6 o 'clock!
I'll be late for dinner!
I guess we might as well call
it a day and log out, too.
Rich girls and their problems, am I right?
I can't believe he's still asleep.
I know, he didn't even feel a thing.
Hey Liz, what's up?
A little while ago, you said you
thought Zekken converted over to ALO.
The way you described the
duels got me thinking.
Could Zekken be someone from SAO?
Mm-hmm.
That's the impression I got after my duel.
I wanted a second opinion, so after Kirito
lost his, I asked him what he thought.
So what did Kirito have to say?
He said that even though the
skills were through the roof,
Zekin's definitely not a player from SAO.
That's not all.
Kirito also said that if
Zekken really was from SAO,
the dual-wielding skill
wouldn't have gone to him.
It would have gone to Zekken.
I want to show you
what I want
to
show you.
I'll always be able to confirm that
I'll always be able to confirm.
I don't know how long
you are, but you are sure
I'll always be able to confirm.
I'll always be able to see you.
Next time, Zekken.